# Ian Brown i.mayo.brown@gmail.com | https://imayobrown.github.io

#### **Profile**

I am a software developer/engineer currently focused on building scalable network applications. I enjoy learning new software technologies with the aim of using them to solve interesting problems. I am productive in both individual and team-based environments and have design, development and implementation experience on multiple projects.

## **Skills**

**Languages** – Python, JavaScript, C/C++, C#/.Net, HTML/CSS, Java, SQL, NI LabVIEW **Frameworks/Extensions** – Django, DjangoRestFramework, Backbone.js, jQuery, Require.js **Tools/Platforms** – Git, SVN, Eclipse, Visual Studio, MySQL, MySQL Workbench, SQLite, Node.js, iPython, Linux(Ubuntu), Windows **Other** – unit testing, REST API, JSON, AJAX

## **Employment Experience**

**Software Engineer** | Communications and Power Industries | September 2012 – Present

- Designed, developed, and maintained site wide system to test units and collect data.
- Designed, developed, and launched single page web application and supporting backend to save, retrieve, view, analyze, and distribute cataloged data.
- Developed and maintained, through international travel, embedded software for customer control of RF transmitter systems.
- Designed and implemented GUI's for touch panel control.

### **Education**

#### **Georgia Institute of Technology**

January 2015 - Present | M.S. Computer Science | GPA: 4.0

#### **University of Massachusetts, Amherst**

September 2008 – May 2012 | B.S. Physics/Mathematics | GPA: 3.8

• Member of the University Commonwealth Honors College

## **Research Experience**

#### **Research Assistant**

September 2010 – June 2012 | University of Massachusetts, Amherst | Tuominen Group

• Conducted experiments probing the characteristics of the Kosterlitz-Thouless transition in two-dimensional superconducting films of aluminum for undergraduate honors thesis.

**Summer Research Internship** | University of Massachusetts, Amherst | Tuominen Group June 2011 – September 2011

• Continued research on the Kosterlitz-Thouless transition in two-dimensional superconducting films.